[{"answer": "Well, praying does help.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "Is this going to come to praying again?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "I have been unfaithful to my wife.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "(voice over): And remember this?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "I don't find it negative at all.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "It is a negative thing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Yes, because I think it is a deliberately provocative stance that you take.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Do I really anger you?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "I don't know if you have seen the \"Book of Mormon\" of Matt Stone and Trey Parker?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "I believe in this superior being, a God.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Well, let me ask you, how did we get here?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Because I have never heard an atheist explain to me --", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Why do you need to label that as something that is God or something?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Well, the answer to saying we can't understand it, is not an answer.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "And what happens at the end of our lives?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "So how do you think that we got here?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "What do you think happens when you die?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Where do you go, I mean when you die.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Where do you go?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "You must be terrified of death?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "How scared are you of 1890.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "But what do you think happens to you?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "1890, yeah.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "1890?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "You weren't alive then, right?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "Is that a horror to you?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "I'm not horrified by any sort of dying, because I believe you go on to a celestial place which is wonderful.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "So why is 2090 any worse than that?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Because I come back to the issue of creation.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Where is your evidence of the celestial place?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "You cannot write a book basically telling a bunch of people around the world, billions of people, who believe in God.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Aren't those the same answer?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "We are all a bit crazy though, a bit nuts?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Yeah, Thor.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "Thor?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Because it is not the same thing and you know it, and you are being deliberately perverse.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "ORGAN: No, but I have an respect for anybody from any religion that has a spiritual and religious conviction and belief in a godlike entity in their lives.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "OK, OK, so you are saying that all the Muslim God, the God of Hindu, the Gods of God of Catholics and Protestants are all the same God, even though there are different rules?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "I don't think that to comfort them I lie to them.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Tough to comfort them in this terrible time?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "I believe touching it might be wrong.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "And you have never touched alcohol?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "I don't drink alcohol, no.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "But you don't drink alcohol?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "I don't do-drink caffeine.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "You don't do drugs?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "No, although my wife exists during the night.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "You don't fornicate with ladies of the night?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "I have-when I say I haven't drank, I really mean it.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "You don't gamble?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Because there is nothing I like doing more than I like than my show.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "And why would you live in Las Vegas?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Well, praying does help.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "It is going to come to praying again?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "I always seem to think that the most important thing is individuals.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "What is the answer?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I am not sure that is exactly the way I see it.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "It is why you vote people, and why they get elected, it is why they run for office?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "I think that the solution is probably to do a little bit of that.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Is the solution to give them government money?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "You have to get the revenues from the higher owners, in my view.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "So you think that raising-not on the small business people would do it?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Well, I'm talking about it.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Yes, and I assume that you are helping them?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "I do give money.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "But you are also giving them money and so on, I assume?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "They do?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "I think most people-", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "You don't think you can help people directly?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "I think, you know, you've got Kiva (ph), doing these microloans all over the world that are making huge changes without any government force, at all.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "What I would do is I think make the government much, much smaller.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "What is the one thing you would do, if you were president, to get Americans back to work?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "ORGAN: When we come back, I want to talk you about magic.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Just to shut me up?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Yes, my son's name is my wife's maiden name.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Your two kids are called Zolten Penn and a Moxie Crime Fighter?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Moxie, this is one -- Moxie, as you may not know, not being from our wonderful country, Moxie is the beverage, it is an American brand name out of Maine, called Moxie, that then went into -- it is one of the odd brand names that went into the dictionary, not as like Coke meaning soda, but rather as meaning guts, gumption, and so on.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Moxie Crime Fighter?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "No, no, it is better than that.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Is she old enough to realize what you have done?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Does it feel like a marriage to you?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "There was no sort of cuddly feeling for him.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "You like him?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Wonderfully.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "How do you get along now?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "ILLETTE: About twice a year, we go out socially together.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Do you socialize away from work?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "No, no, no, no, no.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Do you do all of the talking?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "More so than me.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "So he's perfectly garrulous when you have dinner and stuff?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "I would pray for, I think, more perfect knowledge.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "What would you pray for?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Why was it surprising?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "I can't hammer nails for the rest of my life.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "What would you hope to gain from this?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "You know, I don't think that there is a lot to gained by the \"might have been\" or the \"would have been\", or the \"could have beens\" of life.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "When you have seen what has happened to America and you have seen the emergence of the Tea Party as a proper formidable political force, do you feel a twinge of regret that you are not at the forefront of this?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "I would say I absolutely believe in the notion of tax reform.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "The super rich who are paying a disproportionate sum of taxes in their total tax threshold, compared to the guy compared on the street?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "I think that the primary system will winnow that out.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Which of the Republicans, at the moment-and we are seeing a clear pattern beginning to emerge with Romney, and Bachmann and Perry and so on-who do you think fundamentally has what it takes in the overall package to seriously challenge Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Well, I'm saying you are in the paddock.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Well, you are trying to get me to pick a horse and I don't want to do that?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Well, I think there is talk of that still happening.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Could you see him rallying to the cause of the party, if no one has emerged by then that people think could beat Obama?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "No, I don't think you could look at it that simplistically.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "So is Michele Bachmann the one in that case, is she the obvious person now beginning to capture enough of the public's imagination to potentially be that person?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "ANFORD: I'm not going to pick a horse.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "But of those names, of the three, you know, which one if you had to put one in the race tomorrow?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "It is humbling.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "How does it feel?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Well, I think that, you -- I mean, anybody who has been married doesn't start out the beginning thinking, boy, I hope some day I get divorced and I hope some day that the train comes off of the track.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Given that, do you feel great regret, or is that the wrong emotion to put to you?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "Well, I have learned a lot.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "And what have you learned about yourself?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "They're incredible.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "How has the public been with you?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "It was fabulous.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "How did that make you feel?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "A whole host of things, none of which are particularly productive in terms of my boys who might be watching the show.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "What would you do differently?", "qSentId": 664}, {"answer": "Yeah, I'd say a couple different things.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "Would anything really have made much difference?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "I hope so.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "Having got it wrong in your marriage, do you feel like you've learned enough from that whole experience, and the bruising exposure and scandal to get it right now?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "Are you happier in yourself now do you think?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "It's true.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "We'll see.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "Do you have any plans to remarry?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 723, "question": "Would it be a nice ending to the saga for you?", "qSentId": 722}, {"answer": "We'll see.", "docId": "110903pmt", "aSentId": 728, "question": "It wouldn't be the most shocking thing we'd read or hear?", "qSentId": 727}]